# Juan Lemos

Personal Information

Name: Juan Lemos Web: <u>juanlemos.com</u>

linkedin.com/in/juan-lemos



## Summary

Software engineer graduated from Universidad Católica del Uruguay. Passionate about learning, making questions and solving problems.

Interested in decision making and business management.

I have worked for more than 2 years into the software development industry with American clients, in diverse teams. My tasks have been to align the software solutions with the client's needs and thinking in the

medium- and long-term consequences.

### Skills

### Programming:

- React
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- NodeJS
- SQL
- Android
- Swift

#### Others:

- English
- Decision making
- Communication
- **Problem-Solving**
- Scrum

## Experience

Tech leader at Octobot Mar 2020 - Present

Full stack developer at Código Del Sur Aug 2017 - Mar 2020

Scholarship at ICT4V (Information and Communication Technologies for Verticals) Sep 2016 - Jul 2017

### Education

IEEM Business school – PJP business programs 2019

Universidad Católica Del Uruguay – Computer engineer 2013 - 2017

# Accomplishments

Full tuition scholarship at Universidad Católica Del Uruguay – Decision making in business 2014

Tuition scholarship at Universidad Católica Del Uruguay 2013